Guide to the Stanford University, Haas Center for Public Service, Records SC0541
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2001-237
  - General Files, Subseries 1
    - Groundbreaking- annotated agenda (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Groundbreaking invitation (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Groundbreaking planning (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Ground Breaking article – Times Tribune 06/03/92 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Groundbreaking press release (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Haas Center opening 4/23/93 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - HCPS open house 10/07/91 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Opening (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Haas Center Celebration 10/10/89 invitation (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Haas event 10/10 89 planning (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Haas event preliminary mailings 08/30/89 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - HCPS photo album mailings 10/17/96 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Reunion Homecoming panel 1996 (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Schools Program summer celebration – July 1992 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Senior reception forms (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Senior reception (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1987 student planning committee (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - You Can Make a Difference student committee list (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - Student committee for You Can Make a Difference conference 1988 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - You Can Make a Difference attendance sheets (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - You Can Make a Difference dinner ‘91 (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - Minority alums ‘95 (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Alumni consulting team- GSB (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Alumni assoc. 1996 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Possible volunteers ‘93 (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Things to do for You Can Make a Difference conference- info sheet (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1987 evaluation summary (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network staff lists 1984-85 (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1988 conference – student forms (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - You Can Make a Difference student committee list (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - SIG students 1986-87 (Box 16, Folder 78)
    - Haas students 1987-89 (Box 16, Folder 79)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network members 1986-90 (Box 16, Folder 80)
    - You Can Make a Difference students 1989-91 (Box 16, Folder 81)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1988 mtg sign-ups (Box 16, Folder 82)
    - HCPS 1989-90 paid and non-paid staff (Box 16, Folder 83)
    - Haas staff list 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 84)
    - Letter to graduates re: being public service career advisors 08/89 (Box 16, Folder 85)
    - 1984-85 public service center summer fellows (Box 16, Folder 86)
    - 1988 public service summer fellows (Box 16, Folder 87)
    - 1984 fellowship winners (Box 16, Folder 88)
    - PSC staff lists 1987-88 (Box 16, Folder 89)
    - List of all permanent staff members (1984-90) (Box 16, Folder 90)
    - HCPS 1989-90 staff list (Box 16, Folder 91)
    - 1989 public service summer fellows (Box 16, Folder 92)
    - 1986 summer fellows (Box 16, Folder 93)
    - 1985 public service summer fellows (Box 16, Folder 94)
    - Public service summer fellows 1984-1991 (Box 16, Folder 95)
    - Haas student lists (Box 16, Folder 96)
    - Teatro Visión (Box 16, Folder 97)
    - Alumni program ideas (Box 16, Folder 98)
    - Eastern Council- alumni (Box 16, Folder 99)
    - A Century of Service publication and mural questionnaire (Box 16, Folder 100)
    - Speech -- Derek Bok 06/06/91 (Box 16, Folder 101)
    - YAPS directory 1994-95 (Box 16, Folder 102)
    - YAPS description (Box 16, Folder 103)
    - YAPS strategy and timeline (Feb. 1995) (Box 16, Folder 104)
    - YAPS undergrad focus group 04/27/95 (Box 16, Folder 105)
    - Article on young alum doing service (Box 16, Folder 106)
    - YAPS notes (Box 16, Folder 107)
    - YAPS EPSSA appeal 1991 (Box 16, Folder 108)
    - YAPS structure committee 03/19/91 (Box 16, Folder 109)
    - Excerpts from letter to HCPS and CPPC (Box 16, Folder 110)
    - Stanford Young Alumni Public Service Network Mission (Box 16, Folder 111)
    - Ad Hoc young Alumni meeting 02/05/91 (Box 16, Folder 112)
    - Letter to Daily editor re: alums and service 07/19/90 (Box 16, Folder 113)
    - Young alums in service panel 02/05/31 (Box 16, Folder 114)
    - Public/Community service young alumnae/i group purposes/pan July 1990 (Box 16, Folder 115)
    - YAPS 1996 correspondence (Box 16, Folder 116)
    - Young Alums 1990 correspondence (Box 16, Folder 117)
    - Public and community service course development fund (Box 16, Folder 118)
    - ‘Public Service and the Curriculum’ a summary report 03/91 (Box 16, Folder 119)
    - Wingspread special report (1989) (Box 16, Folder 120)
    - Summer institution on service learning (Box 16, Folder 121)
    - Academic study and public service – student manual (Box 16, Folder 122)
    - Internship learning class (Box 16, Folder 123)
    - Service Learning Center (Box 16, Folder 124)
    - Service Learning 2000 Center (Box 16, Folder 125)
    - Stanford Summer Institute on Service learning (Box 16, Folder 126)
    - Service-Learning Network (Box 16, Folder 127)
    - Binder- strengthening connections between service and learning 1991 (Box 16, Folder 128)
    - 1991 Campus Compact Summer Institute on Integrating Service with Academic Study July 22-26, 1191 (Box 16, Folder 129)
    - SL program management- internal resources (Box 16, Folder 130)
    - HCPS staff poster 11/05/97 (Box 16, Folder 131)
    - Faculty Service Learning Institute affinity groups 1997 (Box 16, Folder 132)
    - Faculty Service-Learning Institute Sept. 6-8, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 133)
    - Palo Alto vs. East Palo Alto facts (Box 16, Folder 134)
    - Annual report 1995-96 (Box 16, Folder 135)
    - Haas website info (Box 16, Folder 136)
    - ‘Looking Forward/Looking Back: Tales from a Decade of Service’ program flyer (Box 16, Folder 137)
    - H&S Quarterly- article on Luis Fraga (Box 16, Folder 138)
    - ‘From the Halls of Congress to the Neighborhoods of our Nation’ welfare policy discussion 02/20/98 (Box 16, Folder 139)
    - Faculty Steering Committee meeting 02/24/98 (Box 16, Folder 140)
    - Letters from EPASSA students and teachers to EPASSA supporters 1997 (Box 16, Folder 141)
    - EPASSA student survey summer 1997 (Box 16, Folder 142)
    - Service profiles and interviews 1997 (Box 16, Folder 143)
    - You Can Make a Difference profiles and interviews (Box 16, Folder 144)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1987 memos re: Don Kennedy’s possible cancellation (Box 16, Folder 145)
    - Catherine Milton (CM) correspondence w/ Jim Rosse (Box 16, Folder 146)
    - CM- article (Box 16, Folder 147)
    - CM- FYI materials (Box 16, Folder 148)
    - Coalition for Educational and Cultural Advancement (Box 16, Folder 149)
    - Student Center for Innovation in Research and Education (SCIRE) (Box 16, Folder 150)
    - Catherine Milton (CM) bio (Box 16, Folder 151)
    - Memo re: Rhodes and Marshall scholarships (Box 16, Folder 152)
    - Haas building project correspondence (Box 16, Folder 153)
    - CM- space problems (Box 16, Folder 154)
    - Budget/centennial materials 01/25/85 (Box 16, Folder 155)
    - CM- appointment as lecturer in the public policy program 02/19/85 (Box 16, Folder 156)
    - Correspondence 1989 (Box 16, Folder 157)
    - 1998-99 Public Service Scholars (Box 16, Folder 158)
    - STEPS in D.C. – Stanford Exchange for Public Service 1988 (Box 16, Folder 159)
    - Service Learning presentation by Wade Brynelson (Box 16, Folder 160)
    - Address by Pres. Nelson Mandela on receiving honorary Harvard Doctorate 09/18/98 (Box 16, Folder 161)
    - 1998-99 Haas calendar (Box 16, Folder 162)
    - Service-learning at Santa Clara University (Box 16, Folder 163)
    - 1999 Public Service Scholars theses presentations (Box 16, Folder 164)
    - National Society for Experiential Education (Box 16, Folder 165)
    - Haas server analysis (Box 16, Folder 166)
    - Summer educational, employment, and athletic programs for youth 1999 (Box 16, Folder 167)
    - Faculty Steering Committee Agenda for May 18 Meeting, 5/10/99 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Steering Committee minutes 03/01/99 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Dimensions of Public Service Education draft (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Management Assistant job description (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Women Working for Change (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Class of 1999 Haas events (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - EPA Charter School Enrichment Program (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Comments on Haas Center experience (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Commons Spring 1998/99 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Quotes (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Tutor survey responses- academic year 1998-99 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Public Service Leaders Pilot Program 06/17/99 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Public Service Program for Community Leadership (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - 7th Street/McClymonds Corridor Neighborhood Improvement Initiative 05/24/99 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Community Impact (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Budget Projections 1999- EPASSA, Schools, Community Partnerships (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Community Service Work-Study Program (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Memo re: scheduling meetings 05/20/99 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Website upgrades 1999 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Student Groups, Subseries 2
    - Haas Center student group information (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Haas Center affiliation policy (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Haas Center affiliated student groups (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Affiliated student groups 1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Haas Center service organizations (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Financial Support of Student Organizations (1994) (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Financial Support of Student Organizations (cont.) (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Financial Support of Student Organizations 1995 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Haas Center Student Organizations Fund ('94-95) (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Student Organizations Fund Recipients (1994-95) (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Student Organizations Fund 1995 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Haas Student Organizations Fund Applications 1995 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Haas Student Organizations Fund Requests 1995 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Haas Student Organizations Fund Requests (cont.) (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - 1995 Student Organizations Fund- Recipients 1995 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Student Organizations Fund Rejections WTR 1995 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Student Organizations Fund Rejections WTR 1995 cont. (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Student Organizations Fund WTR 1995-Misc. Info (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Student Organizations Fund 1995-96 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Student Organizations Fund Spring 1996 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Student Organizations Fund 1996 Recipients (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Student Organizations Fund-Interviews (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Student Organizations Fund (1996) Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - United Students for Veterans Health (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Volunteers in Health (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Delta Sigma theta Sorority, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Alpha Phi Omega Fraternity (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Stanford High School education Program (SHEP) (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Students for Environmental Action at Stanford (SEAS) (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - La Raza (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Project Save news clippings (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Volunteers in Asia (VIA) (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Ravenswood Reads (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Students for Environmental Action (SEAS) (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - East Palo Alto Neighborhood Improvement Initiative (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - One East Palo Alto (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - East Palo Alto Tennis and Tutoring (EPATT) (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Alternative Spring Break (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Alternative Spring Break 1992: Youth in Action: East Palo Alto (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - East Palo Alto Stanford Summer Academy (EPASSA) Program report '86 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - EPASSA 1990 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Misc. EPASSA info (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Stanford Upward Bound (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Upward Bound 1989 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Stanford Upward Bound annual budget (1992-93) (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Upward Bound publicity (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - S*E*A*C misc. materials (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - S*E*A*C resources (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - S*E*A*C 1991 Threshold (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - S*E*A*C 1992 Threshold (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - S*E*A*C 1993 Threshold editions (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - S*E*A*C 1994 Threshold (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - S*E*A*C 1995 Threshold (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Student Environmental Action Coalition (S•E•A•C)- "Threshold": 1997 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Stanford Model United Nations revival 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Model UN sessions (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Stanford MUN- meeting minutes (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Stanford Model UN budget/financial docs (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Stanford Model United Nations new clippings (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Stanford Model UN- Reading materials (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 'The Model United Nations' video (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Model UN misc. materials" (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - SIG [Stanford in Government] Description (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Stanford in Government: The Vision (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Stanford in Government (1989-90) (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - SIG programs & services (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - SIG programming/events (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - SIG Programming (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Stanford in Government fundraising (1992) (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - SIG: Special fee campaign (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - SIG thank-you letters (1992) (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Stanford in Government Small donor letters (1993) (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Stanford in Government Fellowship program (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - SIG Fellowship application (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - SIGnificant News- SIG (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - SIG Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - SIG- Approaching Washington (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Stanford in Washington (1993-94) (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Stanford in Washington (1994-95) (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Stanford in Government campus planning (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Stanford in Government campus opening/ dedication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - D.C. Campus fundraising proposal (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Stanford in Government campus/budget planning (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Stanford in Government budgets (1987-88 thru. 1990-91) (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Stanford in Government Program Committee (1996) (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Stanford in Government Program Committee (1998) (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Stanford in Government Program Committee ('98-'99) (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Stanford Local Government Internship Program (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - RotaCare Volunteer Corp intro hand-outs (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - RotaCare Reading materials (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - RotaCare Finances (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - RotaCare Demographics (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - RotaCare Clinic Patient load 01/98-06/98 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - RotaCare recruiting materials (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - RotaCare Volunteer Corp applications (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - RotaCare Volunteer Corp application cont. (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - RotaCare physicians & volunteers (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Stanford Area RotaCare Clinic volunteer evaluations (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - RotaCare: Orientation handouts (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - RotaCare Clinics misc. info (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Stanford Area RotaCare Clinic (2000) (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Stanford Community Service Faire (1983) (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Stanford Community Service Faire (1985) (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Stanford Community Service Faire (1986) (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Stanford Community Service Faire (1987) (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - YAPS description (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - YAPS Structure (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - YAPS Mission/value statements & goals (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - YAPS Steering committee (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - YAPS Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - disk 'YAPS' - YAPS article 12/11/92 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Young Alums in Public Service Meetings (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - YAPS Survey 1992 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - YAPS Projects (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Drum Major for Justice Fellowship (YAPS) (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - YAPS RAPS publication (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - YAPS articles (1/1993) (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Young Alums in Public Service (YAPS) 1990-91 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - YAPS 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - YAPS 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - YAPS 1993 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Public Service Network - informational materials (1989-1991) (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Public Service Network: Programs 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Public Service Network- memos/ correspondence (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Public Service Network Notes (1989-91) (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - PSN Calendar 1990-91 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Youth Service of California (YSCal) (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Disk 'Jeremy YSCal': (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Disk 'Jeremy 2': (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Stanford tutoring programs 1986-87 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Youth Opportunities Program 1988 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - EPA youth programs (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - East Palo Alto Youth Council (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Service across Ethnic Centers (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Youth volunteer opportunities (misc.) (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Stanford Anthology for Youth (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Stanford Anthology for Youth publications Vol. 1-2 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Stanford Anthology for Youth publications Vol. 3-4 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Stanford Anthology for Youth publications Vol. 5-6 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS - intro (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS Awards/recognition (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS news clippings (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Stanford AIDS Awareness Week 1995-99 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - HIV/AIDS Roundtables (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS pamphlets/flyers (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS Resource binder 1997-98 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS resource binder cont. I (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS resource binder cont. II (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS resource binder cont. III (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS resources: news articles (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS resources: articles & news clippings (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS resources: Newsletters (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS resources: Flyers (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS resources: The Names Project (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS resources: AIDS Community Research Consortium (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS resources: Positively Aware (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS resources: Ellipse Peninsula AIDS Services (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS resources: San Mateo County AIDS Program (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS resources: Project Inform (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS resources: Misc. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS resources (misc.) (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS resources: pamphlets (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network - Constitution 1986 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network purpose/ partners/ activities (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network- misc. financial info (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Finances (1985-86) (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network Scrap Book 1986-87 (Box 4, Folder 22-23)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network Articles 1987-88 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Projects (summer) 1988 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network 1988-89 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network -- 'The Networker' 1992-92 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network -- 'The Networker' various issues (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network Community Service '88-89 Representative handbook (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Community Service Representative packets (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network (1991-92) binder (Box 4, Folder 31-34)
  - You Can Make a Difference, Student Groups, and Miscellaneous Files, Subseries 3
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference- background Info (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - Chronological history of You Can Make a Difference Conference (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - Structure-You Can Make a Difference Conference (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - You Can Make a Difference Workshops (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - You Can Make a Difference Subject/Task Discussions (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - You Can Make a Difference registration form (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - You Can Make a Difference & Stanford Volunteer Network (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1987 - Faculty-Staff evaluation meeting 12/02/87 (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1987 - Misc. Info (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1988-1987 Evaluation Assessment (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference In-house Planners' Manual 1989 (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1990 Summary (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1990 Evaluation Info (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1991 Invitation (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - 1991 You Can Make a Difference Evaluations Information (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Notes from You Can Make a Difference Topic/Format Brainstorming 12/06/92 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - 1992 You Can Make a Difference evaluations (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1992 Summary of Evaluation Forms (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - 1993 You Can Make a Difference Proposal 08/26/92 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1993- planning (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1993- financial information" (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1993 publicity (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference 1993 pamphlets/programs (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1993 informational meeting agenda (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1993 meetings (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - 1993 You Can Make a Difference volunteer forms/applications (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1993 agenda (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1993 program (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1993 addendum (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - 1993 You Can Make a Difference Overview (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1993 organization chart (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Consultants- You Can Make a Difference 1993 (07/92) (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference 1993 organizers (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1993 Steering Committee (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1993 report and review (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1993- volunteer brochure (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - You Can Make A Difference Conference- Kresge tapes (1995) (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1993 transcripts (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - You Can Make a Difference 1993 directed reading- Prof. Fraga (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - You Can Make a Difference Office Hours 1992-93 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - 1993 You Can Make a Difference Evaluations (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Post You Can Make a Difference 1993 Conference Materials (Box 6, Folder 24)